Alarm frocks, greensights, zoos like a pro.
The two pairs of eyes say, come on, let's go!
The leash is a mess, they're tangled again.
I know they need to go, just don't know when.
Don't thought be yet, but they don't care.
They're sniffing every pole, every tree, every chair.
I swear they're in potty, dragged me to the park.
Damn, the way we always have, we always breath, why I?
Tudum for one minstrel, please.
And the regaist, that's a poor bastard beast.
I'm the unboss, show me more of the daily parade.
All the sidewalks spread for my gig night faves.
Tudum for one minstrel, please.
Neighbors wave, I pretend I'm the console, but B.O.'
's walkin' M.T.O.
Juki's biting the mailman's shoe, I'm yelling their names like a fuckbot that's who.
This isn't exercise, this is urban combat, I'm dodging scooters, strollers, and a psycho jet.
Some days I dream of a robot pup, but them men look at me and I just shut up.
Two dogs, one leash, no peace.
I am so stretched like a Jesus beast.
I'm the clown barge out of a cave parade.
Every morning, BLs find a hand grenade.
Two dogs, one leash, no peace.
A little bit like Cooper Day, but it's sane.
Chase these squirrels, I'll give that cocaine.
And when we're home, I name.
Babe, just trash and stone.
Why bandage wounds from a civil war?
Two dogs, one leash, no peace.
Call the U.N.
for a parking cease.
But tomorrow at dawn we'll be out again.
Just a guy, his dogs and zero sand.
Two dogs, one leash, no peace.